<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Entity>
  <Name>Massachusetts</Name>
  <Code>MA</Code>
  <SupportInformation array="true">
    <Section html="true"><![CDATA[<h4>Phone Support</h4>
      <p class="bwi-support-intro">For private well questions please contact Massachusetts Department of Environmental Protection’s Drinking Water Program:</p>
      <ul class="plain-list bwi-resources-list">
        <li>
          <p class="bwi-resource-name">Massachusetts Department of Environmental Protection</p>
          <p>Drinking Water Program</p>
          <p>1 Winter Street</p>
          <p>Boston, MA 02108</p>
          <p><i class="fa fa-phone"></i>(617) 292-5770</p>
          <p><i class="fa fa-send"></i>Program.Director-DWP@state.ma.us</p>
        </li>
      </ul>]]></Section>
    <Section html="true"><![CDATA[<h4>Additional Resources</h4>
            <ul class="plain-list bwi-resources-list">
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">Centers for Disease Control and Prevention</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://www.cdc.gov">https://www.cdc.gov</a></p>
                <p>1600 Clifton Rd</p>
                <p>Atlanta, GA 30329</p>
                <p>800-CDC-INFO (800-232-4636)</p>
                <p>TTY: (888) 232-6348</p>
                <p>Contact CDC–INFO: <br><a target="_blank" href="https://wwwn.cdc.gov/dcs/ContactUs/Form">https://wwwn.cdc.gov/dcs/ContactUs/Form</a></p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">EPA (Environmental Protection Agency):</p>
                <p>Inquiries specific to groundwater and drinking water can be submitted to an information specialist through the EPA Safe Drinking Water Hotline at 1-800-426-4791 <br><a target="_blank" href="https://www.epa.gov/ground-water-and-drinking-water/forms/online-form-epas-office-ground-water-and-drinking-water">https://www.epa.gov/ground-water-and-drinking-water/forms/online-form-epas-office-ground-water-and-drinking-water</a></p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">You can also send mail to:</p>
                <p>EPA Office of Ground Water and Drinking Water</p>
                <p>1200 Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W. (Mail Code 4606M)</p>
                <p>Washington, D.C. 20460</p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">MassDEP Drinking Water Program's Private Wells Information</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/private-wells">https://www.mass.gov/private-wells</a></p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">MassDEP Drinking Water Program's Private Well Guidelines</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/media/1514836">https://www.mass.gov/media/1514836</a></p>
                <p>These guidelines provide information regarding many different aspects of private wells, including additional information regarding contaminants not included in the Be Well Informed web tool.</p>
              </li>
              <li>
             <p class="bwi-resource-name">MassDEP Drinking Water Program's Contaminants Web Page</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/lists/contaminants">https://www.mass.gov/lists/contaminants</a></p>
                <p>This web page provides information regarding many different drinking water contaminants.</p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">MassDEP's 2017 Standards & Guidelines for Contaminants in Massachusetts Drinking Water Web Page</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/guides/drinking-water-standards-and-guidelines">https://www.mass.gov/guides/drinking-water-standards-and-guidelines</a></p>
                <p>This web page provides additional information regarding how each of the health-based drinking water standards were established.</p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">MassDEP Information Regarding Arsenic and Uranium in Bedrock Wells</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/arsenic-uranium-bedrock-well-study">https://www.mass.gov/arsenic-uranium-bedrock-well-study</a></p>
                <p>This web page provides information regarding arsenic and uranium in bedrock wells in Massachusetts including maps of areas with increased probability of naturally occurring arsenic and uranium contamination in well water; information regarding treatment methods for arsenic and radiological contaminants; and a list of MassDEP certified laboratories that conduct arsenic testing in drinking water, including some that offer arsenic speciation testing.</p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">MassDEP Well Drillers Program</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/well-driller-program">https://www.mass.gov/well-driller-program</a></p>
                <p>This site provides a list of MassDEP Certified Well Drillers.</p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">Cooperative Extension - Home Water Treatment Devices</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="http://articles.extension.org/pages/31581/home-water-treatment-devices#.VIdCJcgo7cs">http://articles.extension.org/pages/31581/home-water-treatment-devices#.VIdCJcgo7cs</a></p>
                <p>This site provides information regarding many types of home water treatment systems.</p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">Cooperative Extension - Selecting a Home Water Treatment System</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="http://articles.extension.org/pages/31580/selecting-a-home-water-treatment-system">http://articles.extension.org/pages/31580/selecting-a-home-water-treatment-system</a></p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">NGWA Wellowner.org</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="http://wellowner.org/">http://wellowner.org/</a></p>
                <p>This site provides well drilling, maintenance, water testing, and water treatment information for well owners.</p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">Massachusetts Department of Public Health</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/orgs/department-of-public-health">https://www.mass.gov/orgs/department-of-public-health</a></p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">Dartmouth Toxic Metals Superfund Research Program</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="http://www.dartmouth.edu/~toxmetal/index.html">http://www.dartmouth.edu/~toxmetal/index.html</a></p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">USGS-New England Water Science Center-Massachusetts Office</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="https://ma.water.usgs.gov/">https://ma.water.usgs.gov/</a></p>
              </li>
              <li>
                <p class="bwi-resource-name">NSF – The Public Health and Safety Organization</p>
                <p><a target="_blank" href="http://www.nsf.org/consumer-resources/water-quality/water-filters-testing-treatment/home-water-treatment-system-selection">http://www.nsf.org/consumer-resources/water-quality/water-filters-testing-treatment/home-water-treatment-system-selection</a></p>
              </li>
            </ul>]]></Section>
    <Section html="true"><![CDATA[<h4>MassDEP Certified Laboratories for Testing Drinking Water</h4>
            <ul class="bwi-lab-list">
              <li><a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/certified-laboratories">https://www.mass.gov/certified-laboratories</a></p>
              </li></ul>]]></Section>
  </SupportInformation>
  <Results>
    <Heading><![CDATA[The Commonwealth of Massachusetts<br>
     DEPARTMENT OF ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION<br>
     Results from the MassDEP Be Well Informed Guide]]></Heading>
    <Introduction><![CDATA[<p>Information provided in this report is for informational purposes only and should not be substituted for direct consultation with a qualified water treatment professional. Other conditions or factors related to your well or home not considered by this online guide may determine the most appropriate water treatment option. Please be aware that the Be Well Informed tool focuses on contaminants that are most  commonly of concern and doesn’t include all contaminant testing that MassDEP Drinking Water Program recommends for private drinking water wells nor all contaminants for which drinking water health advisories or guidelines have been established. For example, specifically, the Be Well Informed Tool currently doesn’t include any volatile organic compound (VOC) contaminants nor several emerging contaminants, such as PFAS that may be of concern in some locations.  MassDEP's <a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/media/1514836">Private Well Guidelines</a> provide information regarding additional contaminants that may be of concern based upon site-specific information.</p>]]></Introduction>
    <AboutTheResults><![CDATA[<p>Massachusetts does not have a requirement for testing private wells, nor are there any statewide regulatory standards for water quality in private wells. However testing of private wells is recommended.  In Massachusetts the regulation of private wells falls under the jurisdiction of the local boards of health or health departments.  There may be water quality or water treatment requirements in your local municipality that may differ from the information provided in this report.  Based on what you entered from your laboratory report, the Results Summary below indicates whether your water meets federal and state health-based standards for public water systems (Maximum Contaminant Levels - MCLs) as well as other standards and guidelines for public water systems (Secondary Maximum Contaminant Levels - SMCLs, health advisory levels, Action Levels - ALs, etc.). These standards and guidelines are often referred to as "limits" on your laboratory report. If your water exceeds or is approaching established federal/state drinking water limits or advisory levels for public water systems for the contaminant(s) entered, additional health information and treatment options will be shown.</p>]]><![CDATA[<p>Exceeding a standard does not necessarily mean someone’s health will be adversely impacted. Public drinking water standards are set to be health-protective and include a margin of safety that accounts for exposure to sensitive individuals, exposures from other sources (such as food), and other factors. The health risk from exposure to any substance depends on how much someone is exposed to, how long the exposure lasted, and how someone is exposed. Possible harm may also depend on personal factors such as health status, age, sex, diet, lifestyle, family history, and work history.</p>]]><![CDATA[<p>See MassDEP's <a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/guides/drinking-water-standards-and-guidelines">Drinking Water Standards & Guidelines</a> for additional information regarding how each of the health-based drinking water standards were established.  Information regarding a specific contaminant may be obtained by clicking on the contaminant's name where it appears in the "substance" columns in the contaminant tables.</p>]]></AboutTheResults>
    <WaterTreatmentSystem>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Print this report and make final water treatment decisions with a qualified &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.wqa.org/Programs-Services/Resources/Find-Providers/Find-Certified-Professionals"&gt;water treatment professional.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;More Information about selecting appropriate water treatment devices is available from &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.nsf.org/consumer-resources/water-quality/water-filters-testing-treatment/home-water-treatment-system-selection"&gt;NSF&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://articles.extension.org/pages/31581/home-water-treatment-devices#.VIdCJcgo7cs"&gt;Cooperative Extension&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;More Information is available from &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.mass.gov/drinking-water-program"&gt;MassDEP&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.epa.gov/dwstandardsregulations"&gt;US EPA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</WaterTreatmentSystem>
    <Key>
      <MeetsLimit><![CDATA[Meets the Drinking Water Limit]]></MeetsLimit>
      <CloseToLimit><![CDATA[Close to the Drinking Water Limit]]></CloseToLimit>
      <AboveLimit><![CDATA[Above the Drinking Water Limit]]></AboveLimit>
      <Consult><![CDATA[Consult Additional Message in the Results Details]]></Consult>
    </Key>
  </Results>
</Entity>